keycompete.com 2015-06-03

# HireGEMS® - Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

#### hireGEMS Billing and Agreement Terms of Use

**Ownership and Right to Make Changes**

hireGEMS is an online service owned and operated by HRgems, Inc. who has the right, without notice, to change the look, feel, format of the website, any and all fees and prices charged or collected for credits to be used toward service and for services delivered;

**Scope of Use and User Email**

email addresses are not used in marketing lists and are maintained in the program;

**Intellectual Property**

The materials on the hireGEMS site are copyrighted and protected by all United States and international copyright laws and unlawful copying will be considered infringement;

**No Warranties**

The hireGEMS website is provided “as is” and contains no express, statutory or implied warranties;

**Fees for Credits**

Credits are purchased and used to launch services at the time of purchase or at a later date. Sales of all credits are final, non-refundable and with the sole purpose and value to launch hireGEMS services;

**Use of Credits**

A Credit is spent and deducted from the My Credit number of credits at the time a service is launched. This occurs before it is completed by an applicant or third party for launches on the iPad or tablet or device and before it is completed by an applicant or third party for launches to an email address.

##### Disclaimer

The information on this Web site is provided by HRgems, Inc.. Although we make every effort to keep the information as accurate as possible, HRgems, Inc. disclaims any representation about its accuracy, completeness or appropriateness. When using the information contained on this site, you understand and agree that you assume full responsibility for its use and that hireGEMS is neither responsible nor liable for any claim, loss, or damage resulting from that use.

Information on this Web site may be changed or updated without notice. Information may be out of date at any given time and HRgems, Inc. has no obligation to update information presented on this Web site. HRgems, Inc. may also make improvements and/or changes in services described in this information without notice.

#### Internet Security and Privacy Statement

HRgems, Inc. is committed to maintaining strict standards when protecting the privacy of the information contained on its Web site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site and all other Web sites owned and operated by HRgems, Inc.. HRgems, Inc. can be contacted by mail at PO Box 110550, Naples, FL 34108

**1\. Collecting and Using Personal Information**

HRgems, Inc. will not collect personal information about you, unless you provide us that information voluntarily. If you do elect to provide personal information to us voluntarily, in no case will we sell, license or transmit for any reason that information, unless required to do so by legal, judicial or governmental proceedings, unless necessary for our contractors or agents to perform certain functions for us, or unless we do so in accordance with your authorization.

**2\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**

HRgems, Inc. may collect and/or track (1) the home server domain, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to Colorado Access’ Web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with HRgems, Inc. via e-mail, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forums, registration forms, surveys, e-mail and other online avenues (including demographic and personal profile data), and (4) aggregate and user-specific information on which pages visitors access.

HRgems, Inc. may temporarily place Internet ‘cookies’ on our visitors’ hard drives. A ‘cookie’ is a non-executable element of data that a Web site can send to your browser when you link to that site. These Internet ‘cookies’ assist with saving data about you and your specific preferences, such as your name, password, user-name, any screen preferences, and the pages of a site viewed by you and provides continuity of usage while on the web site. When you disconnect from our site, the ‘cookie’ will be discarded. Some web sites place ‘cookies’ permanently on visitors computers; however, HRgems, Inc. does not follow this practice.

**3\. Linking to Other Sites**

This site may provide links to other sites not owned or controlled by HRgems Inc., that we think may be useful or of interest to you. We cannot, however, be responsible for the content or privacy practices used by other site owners.

**4\. Changes to this Statement**

The foregoing Web Privacy Statement is effective as of January 9, 2013. HRgems, Inc. may change this statement from time to time. This Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**5\. Internet Security Statement**

At HRgems, Inc, we value your online security. For this reason, we have implemented safeguards to protect the information you transmit to us over the internet as described in this notice. We collect and use the information you provide to us to respond to your needs, service your accounts and provide you with information about other services we provide. This statement applies to all users ofwww.hiregems.com, whether or not the user is a HRgems, Inc customer.

#### Web Site Security

At HRgems, Inc, we strive to safeguard your online security. All information provided by customers visiting our web site is kept strictly confidential, to prevent the unauthorized use of the information. All the nonpublic personal information we receive from our customers at HRgems, Inc, whether via phone, mail or the internet, is treated confidentially, as outlined in our privacy policy.

##### SSL Certificate

HRgems, Inc is protected by an SSL Certificate issued by Network Solutions, a trusted internet innovator for over 10 years. SSL stands for Secure Sockets Layer, which is the standard security technology for creating an encrypted link between a web server and a browser. This link ensures that all data passed between the web server and browser remains private and secure. All Secure Link SSL certificates from Network Solutions are encrypted at 128 bits, which is the highest encryption level available. Your will know you have created an SSL link with our web server during the checkout process by seeing the “https://” at the beginning of the URL, as well as seeing the padlock icon (available in most but not all browsers) in the lower right-hand frame of your Web browser.

##### Powerful 128-bit Encryption

128-bit encryption means that the data cryptographically encoded during an SSL session is at the highest level currently available, and nearly impossible to break. Compared to a 40-bit encrypted SSL certificate, a 128-bit is more than 300 septillion (300,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000) times stronger. All Secure Link SSL certificates from Network Solutions are encrypted at 128 bits.

##### E-Mail Security

Regular internet e-mail is never completely secure. When corresponding to us via e-mail, you should only provide information that is non-sensitive and non-confidential. Please do not furnish us any information of a personal nature that you feel uncomfortable providing to us via e-mail. If you are concerned about the security of your communication, please transmit your correspondence to us using the postal service or telephone. HRgems, Inc is not responsible for the security of information we receive via e-mail.

#### Links to Other Sites

HRgems, Inc may provide links to other internet sites, as a convenience to the persons visiting this web site. If you visit these sites via our web site, you may be asked to provide nonpublic personal information.

Please be aware that HRgems, Inc is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. We suggest that, if you visit other web sites throughwww.hiregems.com(or www.traitset.com.com), you read the privacy policies of each site that you visit, as it may differ from ours. Our privacy policy applies solely to this web site.
